♪ Get
on ♪ ♪ Get on ♪ ♪ Lady, you made it, oh, oh ♪ ♪ The city
quiet, the sun is down ♪ ♪ We're in the glow of the
other side of town ♪ ♪ The beat is calling from a
place I know ♪ ♪ Just follow the sound ♪ ♪ We're
dancing in the neon ♪ Dancing in the neon tonight
The rhythm's heavy
A flashing bright reflected colors in your
eyes. I don't care what the real world wants.
This moment's all that I could ever want. We're
dancing in the neon. Oh, oh, oh. We're moving
till the night is gone. Oh, oh, oh. Forget about
tomorrow. We're shining like a light. Dancing
in the neon tonight.
Don't stop, don't stop the feelin' This music's
got me reelin' Don't stop, don't stop the beat
The beat, beat, beat, beat, beat, beat, beat,
beat, beat, beat, beat, beat, beat, beat, beat,
beat, beat, beat We're dancing in the neons
Tonight We're moving till the night is gone
Forget about tomorrow We're shining like a
light Dancing in the neons Tonight We're
dancing in the neons Tonight
Till the night is gone